tmrzoo.com 2013-09-22

# 

TMRzoo Privacy Policy 

By visiting TMRzoo.com, you agree to and accept all of the following Terms and Conditions contained in the Privacy Policy below. 

***Cookies*** 

Cookies are used at TMRzoo.com in the following manners: 

* TMRzoo uses cookies in order to identify members whom are logged into the site and keep them logged in when they return for a new session.   
* Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on your prior visits to TMRzoo.com.  
* Google's use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to TMRzoo visitors based on their visit to this and/or other sites on the Internet.  
* Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting Google's Ads Settings at http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/ 

You can find out more on opting out of third-party vendor's use of cookies for interest based advertising by visiting http://www.aboutads.info/ 

***TMRzoo Message Board Membership*** 

In compliance with The Children's Online Privacy Protection Act and due to the nature of material presented on this site, you must be over the age of 17 to create an account and actively participate on the site through forum messages and any other means of interaction. 

TMRzoo will not be held responsible for any damages incurred as a result of content which you post in the TMRzoo message board. 

Your Membership can be terminated at any time at the sole discretion of TMRzoo staff. 

Any personal information such as name, mailing address and E-Mail address collected during the registration process is not distributed by TMRzoo. No personal information is ever re-sold to a third party vendor. 

Any comments, contest entries or site interaction you provide may be used for the purpose of attracting members, advertisers, and partners to TMRzoo. 

The views and opinions expressed by members in the TMRzoo Forums and Product Reviews are in no way endorsed or sponsored by TMRzoo, TMR Entertainment, LLC, or their staff. TMRzoo reserves the right to edit or delete any post at its discretion at any time. While freedom of speech is practiced at the TMRzoo, any blatant attacks deemed harmful to other members, consistent posting of pornographic material, or persistent spamming may result in immediate termination of your account. 

***Contests*** 

TMRzoo contests are open to all visitors to the site. Any personal information such as name, mailing address and E-Mail address collected during contest entries is not kept or distributed by TMRzoo, unless a sponsor of the contest has requested it. In this instance, the TMRzoo Member or contest entrant will be asked to agree to offer this information to the sponsor, and only to the sponsor, while entering the contest. No entries are ever re-sold to a third party vendor. 

Winners agree to have their name, city and state (country) displayed on the website when they accept their prize via a confirmation E-Mail. 

***Disclosure*** 

TMRzoo openly volunteers its practices of collecting and applying information submitted by its registered membership base. If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy or about any other aspect of the TMRzoo, TMR Entertainment, LLC and any associated practices please contact us at admin(at)tmrzoo.com 

_Last Updated: August 21, 2013_
